A Guide to the The Road Company Records, 1972-1998
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
The Road Company Records, 1972-1998
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms1998-008
38 Cubic Feet 27 boxes; 1 folder
The Road Company records consist of administrative files, touring information, scripts, video and audiocassettes of productions, and public relations material.
The Road Company
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
The Road Company Records were donated to Special Collections in September 1998. An additional 0.2 cu. ft. of material was received in 2008 and 1.4 cu. ft. of materials were received in 2015.
Historical Information
The Road Company was a community-based theater company in Johnson City, Tennessee, dedicated to the production of new theater reflecting the concerns and interests of the community, based on the premise that theater is a community event. Established in 1972, produced plays about southern community history, frontier experiences in democracy, ancient and modern myths, the moonshine trade, land issues, wild lemons, love stories, and the impact of the world energy situation on Johnson City. Many of the plays performed were original works created for the company. The company worked collaboratively with other community theaters. They closed up production in 1998.
Scope and Content
The Road Company records consist of administrative files, touring information, scripts, video and audiocassettes of productions, and public relations material.
The 2008 accrual includes show posters. The 2015 accrual includes financial documents from 1993-1994 and 1998, as well as several folders of administrative files from 1993-1994.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged chronologically. Undated material is at the end.
The 2008 accrual is in an oversize folder housed in Special Collections. The 2015 accrual is at the end of the collection and remains in its original order.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Local/Regional History and Appalachian South; Community theater
Corporate Names:
The Road Company (Community-basesd theatre organization)
Contents List
- Source catalog, 1971. (Box-folder 1-1)
- Peoples Bicentennial Committee Information, 1972-1976. (Box-folder 1-2)
- Pictures of Americomedia, 1973. (Box-folder 1-3)
- Americomedia contracts, 1973. (Box-folder 1-4 to 1-5 (2 folders))
- Media, 1973. (Box-folder 1-6)
- Letters of review of Americomedia, 1973. (Box-folder 1-7)
- Provisional theater, 1973-1978. (Box-folder 1-8)
- Highlander education information, 1974. (Box-folder 1-9)
- Tennessee Department of Revenue—Sales Tax Exemption, 1975. (Box-folder 1-10)
- Other Theater Campaigns, 1975. (Box-folder 1-11)
- Expansion Arts Grant, 1975. (Box-folder 1-12)
- Programs and Promotional flyers and letters. 1975-1976. (Box-folder 1-13)
- Pictures from "The Momentary Arts of State Making," 1975-1976. (Box-folder 1-14 to 1-15 (2 folders))
- Contracts, 1975-1976. (Box-folder 1-16)
- Americomedia, 1976. (Box-folder 1-17 to 1-18 (2 folders))
- Environmental and Regional Research Associates Project, 1976. (Box-folder 1-19)
- Washington County Bill of Rights Project Final Report and Financial Statements, 1976. (Box-folder 1-20)
- Miscellaneous papers related to Washington County Bill of Rights Committee, 1976. (Box-folder 1-21)
- Publicity Flyers and Media, 1976. (Box-folder 1-22)
- PBC Information, 1976. (Box-folder 1-23)
- Completed Shows and Gigs, 1976-1977. (Box-folder 1-24)
- Newspaper Media, 1976-1978. (Box-folder 1-25)
- Miscellaneous, 1976-1977. (Box-folder 1-26)
- SETC, 1976-1980. (Box-folder 1-27)
- Tennessee Department of Employment Security Quarterly Reports, 1976-1982. (Box-folder 1-28)
- Tennessee Department of Employment Security, 1976-1985. (Box-folder 1-29)
- Report of "The Baltimore Neighborhood Arts Circus" for National Endowment, 1977. (Box-folder 2-1)
- Program notes, 1977. (Box-folder 2-2)
- Slide cue sheets, 1977. (Box-folder 2-3)
- In-kind contributions, 1977. (Box-folder 2-4)
- Schedule and Audience for "Chautauqua '77," 1977. (Box-folder 2-5)
- Radio Ad Script for "Chautauqua '77," 1977. (Box-folder 2-6)
- Press Release for "Chautauqua '77," 1977. (Box-folder 2-7)
- Miscellaneous papers from "Chautauqua '77," 1977. (Box-folder 2-8)
- Publicity News clips for "Chautauqua '77," 1977. (Box-folder 2-9)
- Printed Materials on "Chautauqua '77," 1977. (Box-folder 2-10)
- Bills and expenses, 1977. (Box-folder 2-11)
- Pictures from "Chautauqua '77," 1977. (Box-folder 2-12)
- "Chautauqua '77"—A report to the Tennessee Committee for the Humanities, 1977. (Box-folder 2-13)
- Evaluation of "Chautauqua '77," 1977. (Box-folder 2-14)
- We Refuse to Speculate, 1977. (Box-folder 2-15)
- Tennessee Arts Association, 1977. (Box-folder 2-16)
- Watauga Workshop, 1977. (Box-folder 2-17)
- Completed performances, 1977-1978. (Box-folder 2-18)
- Radio Spots, 1977-1978. (Box-folder 2-19)
- Miscellaneous, 1977-1978. (Box-folder 2-20)
- Report of "Chautauqua '77" for the Tennessee Committee for the Humanities, 1977-1978. (Box-folder 2-21)
- Media Related to Alternate Roots, 1977-1979. (Box-folder 2-22)
- Minutes of Board of Director's Meetings, 1977-1991. (Box-folder 2-23 to 2-25 (3 folders))
- Pictures from "Mountain Whispers," 1978. (Box-folder 2-26)
- "Mountain Whispers," 1978. (Box-folder 2-27)
- American Characters, 1978. (Box-folder 2-28)
- Mapopa Workshop, 1978. (Box-folder 2-29)
- Radio Date Cards, 1978. (Box-folder 2-30)
- Theater Directory, 1978. (Box-folder 2-31)
- Media Related to "Mountain Whispers," 1978. (Box-folder 2-32)
- Down Home Scripts, 1978. (Box-folder 2-33)
- Talent and Booking Agency Rosters Information, 1978. (Box-folder 2-34)
- Boston Contacts, 1978. (Box-folder 2-35)
- Spoleto Festival, 1978. (Box-folder 2-36)
- College Master List, 1978. (Box-folder 2-37)
- "Chautauqua '77" Evaluations, 1978. (Box-folder 2-38)
- Regrant Project Financial Evaluation—Information and Reporting Forms, 1978. (Box-folder 2-39 to 2-40 (2 folders))
- Pictures from "Chucky Duck Joke Company," 1978. (Box-folder 2-41)
- Financial Statements, 1978-1979. (Box-folder 2-42)
- Press Releases, 1978-1979. (Box-folder 2-43)
- American Arts Alliance, Inc., 1978-1979. (Box-folder 2-44)
- Miscellaneous, 1978-1979. (Box-folder 2-45)
- Roots Project 1978-1979. (Box-folder 2-46)
- Interest Letters, 1978-1979. (Box-folder 2-47)
- "Energy in the Tennessee Valley," 1978-1979. (Box-folder 2-48 to 2-49, 3-1 (3 folders))
- Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1979. (Box-folder 3-2)
- IRS letters about Roots, 1978-1980. (Box-folder 3-3)
- Broadside, 1978-1980. (Box-folder 3-4)
- Theater spaces and information, 1978-1980. (Box-folder 3-5)
- Information for board meetings, 1978-1982. (Box-folder 3-6)
- Federal with-holding forms, 1978-1988. (Box-folder 3-7)
- Pictures from "The Flying Lemon Circus," 1979. (Box-folder 3-8)
- "The Flying Lemon Circus" references, 1979. (Box-folder 3-9)
- Tennessee Arts Commission—Proposals Management Package and Membership Campaign, 1979. (Box-folder 3-10)
- Pictures from "Heroes, Hot Dogs, and Apple Pie," 1979. (Box-folder 3-11)
- Annual report, 1979. (Box-folder 3-12)
- TAC/RAP Original Statements, 1979. (Box-folder 3-13)
- Memphis trip information, 1979. (Box-folder 3-14)
- ASTC Mail, 1979. (Box-folder 3-15)
- Project Proposal Related to Tennessee Committee for the Humanities, 1979. (Box-folder 3-16)
- National Theater of the Deaf, 1979. (Box-folder 3-17)
- Demographic Reports, 1979. (Box-folder 3-18)
- Americomedia, 1979. (Box-folder 3-19)
- Home Season Information, 1979. (Box-folder 3-20)
- Directors 2000 committee, 1979. (Box-folder 3-21)
- Education Directories, 1979. (Box-folder 3-22)
- SAF Workshop Information, 1979. (Box-folder 3-23)
- Cabaret Correspondence, 1979. (Box-folder 3-24)
- NECAA, 1979. (Box-folder 3-25)
- Completed Performances, 1979. (Box-folder 3-26)
- Brochure Information, 1979. (Box-folder 3-27)
- Thank you letters, 1979. (Box-folder 3-28)
- Tour contracts and interest letters, 1979. (Box-folder 3-29)
- Booking brochures, 1979. (Box-folder 3-30)
- Where's Gradey?, 1979. (Box-folder 3-31)
- Energy Foundation for Economic Health, 1979. (Box-folder 3-32)
- Corner Rooms Transcriptions, 1979. (Box-folder 3-33)
- Form masters, 1979. (Box-folder 3-34)
- TAC panel information, 1979-1980. (Box-folder 3-35)
- TAC/RAP proposal revised, 1979-1980. (Box-folder 3-36)
- AIS, 1979-1980. (Box-folder 3-37)
- Possible Performances, 1979-1980. (Box-folder 3-38)
- Pictures from "Horse Power," 1979-1980. (Box-folder 3-39 to 3-40 (2 folders))
- Miscellaneous, 1979-1980. (Box-folder 3-41)
- National Endowment for the Arts--Expansion Arts, 1979-1980. (Box-folder 3-42)
- Interest correspondence, 1979-1980. (Box-folder 4-1 to 4-3 (3 folders))
- Sponsor Negotiations Records, 1979-1980. (Box-folder 4-4)
- C.E.T.A., 1979-1980. (Box-folder 4-5 to 4-7 (3 folders))
- Performance Arts Center, 1979-1981. (Box-folder 4-8)
- TAC/RAP, 1979-1981. (Box-folder 4-9)
- The Arts Council, 1979-1982. (Box-folder 4-10)
- UAB Loans, 1979-1982. (Box-folder 4-11)
- National Endowment for the Arts Institutional Advancement Grants, 1979-1984. (Box-folder 4-12 to 4-13 (2 folders))
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1979-1991. (Box-folder 4-14 to 4-15 (2 folders))
- Equipment Inventory, 1980. (Box-folder 4-16)
- Fixed Assets, 1980. (Box-folder 4-17)
- Membership meeting, 1980. (Box-folder 4-18)
- Tour information, 1980. (Box-folder 4-19)
- Mid-West Completed Shows, 1980. (Box-folder 4-20)
- Area High Schools, 1980. (Box-folder 5-1)
- Tour Sponsor List (miscellaneous), 1980. (Box-folder 5-2)
- Panel Retreat, 1980. (Box-folder 5-3)
- Sales Strategy, 1980. (Box-folder 5-4)
- Arts Exchange, 1980. (Box-folder 5-5)
- October touring, 1980. (Box-folder 5-6)
- Connecticut Records, 1980. (Box-folder 5-7)
- January touring, 1980. (Box-folder 5-8)
- Summer touring, 1980. (Box-folder 5-9)
- April touring, 1980. (Box-folder 5-10)
- March touring, 1980. (Box-folder 5-11)
- Evaluations of Artists in Schools Program by the Students, 19980. (Box-folder 5-12)
- Child Sexual Assault Prevention Project, 1980. (Box-folder 5-13 to 5-14 (2 folders()
- Artists in Schools Program Related to Tennessee Arts Commission, 1980. (Box-folder 5-15)
- AIS Teacher Evaluation, 1980. (Box-folder 5-16)
- AIS Workshop/Evaluation, 1980. (Box-folder 5-17)
- Old Technical Evaluation Forms, 1980. (Box-folder 5-18)
- "Advancement Grant" Press Announcement, 1980. (Box-folder 5-19)
- Miscellaneous Interest Records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-20)
- D.C. Interactive Records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-21)
- Florida Records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-22)
- Touring Evaluations, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-23)
- Discovery Theater Project by the Smithsonian Institution, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-24)
- North Carolina Inactive Records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-25)
- Illinois and Indiana inactive records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-26)
- Georgia and Kentucky inactive records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-27)
- West Virginia inactive records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-28)
- Mississippi and Alabama inactive records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-29)
- Maryland and Ohio inactive records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-30)
- South Carolina inactive records, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-31)
- Miscellaneous, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-32)
- Annual Report, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-33)
- Annual Report (copy), 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-34)
- Interest Letters, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-35)
- Louisiana Performances, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-36)
- Income Receipt Attachments, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-37)
- TAC Panel Review, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-38)
- ASOLO Touring Theater, 1980-1981. (Box-folder 5-39)
- Office Equipment, 1980-1982. (Box-folder 5-40)
- Tennessee Inactive Records, 1980-1982. (Box-folder 5-41)
- Maine and Pennsylvania Inactive records, 1980-1982. (Box-folder 5-42)
- Virginia Inactive Records, 1980-1982. (Box-folder 5-43)
- Old mailing lists, 1980-1983. (Box-folder 5-44)
- Contributors, 1980-1983. (Box-folder 5-45)
- National Endowment for the Arts—Institutional Advancement—4 year plan, 1980-1984. (Box-folder 5-46 to 5-48 (3 folders))
- 4 year plan, 1980-1984. (Box-folder 5-49)
- Loan Authority, 1980-1987. (Box-folder 5-50)
- TAC Review, 1981. (Box-folder 6-1)
- Levi Strauss CIT, 1981. (Box-folder 6-2)
- Report and Recommendation TAC/RAP, 1981. (Box-folder 6-3)
- Recommendations, 1981. (Box-folder 6-4)
- Workshop Contract Sites, 1981. (Box-folder 6-5)
- East Tennessee Musician's Co-op, 1981. (Box-folder 6-6)
- Subscription Brochure, 1981. (Box-folder 6-7)
- Forms—Financial Statements, 1981. (Box-folder 6-8)
- Spring Tour, 1981. (Box-folder 6-9)
- Fall Tour Evaluations, 1981. (Box-folder 6-10)
- Fall Tour Evaluations, 1981. (Box-folder 6-11)
- Spring Tour, 1981. (Box-folder 6-12)
- Beginning letters for Home Season, 1981. (Box-folder 6-13)
- Rhode Island and Vermont inactive records, 1981. (Box-folder 6-14)
- October Touring, 1981. (Box-folder 6-15)
- September Touring, 1981. (Box-folder 6-16)
- New York, New Jersey, and Massachusetts inactive records, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-17)
- Subscription Season, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-18)
- Business Fundraising letters, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-19)
- North Carolina Contracts (unsuccessful), 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-20)
- Kentucky inactive records, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-21)
- Expo leads, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-22)
- Florida and Georgia inactive records, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-23)
- Mississippi and Alabama inactive records, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-24)
- SAF Touring Proposal, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-25)
- Income Tax Information, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-26)
- National Endowment for the Arts Theater, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-27)
- Programs and Reviews, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-28)
- Journal of Promotional Manager, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-29)
- Tennessee Arts Commission RAP Assistance, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-30)
- Tennessee Committee for the Humanities, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-31 to 6-32 (2 folders))
- Sponsor Negotiations Record (Unsuccessful), 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-33 to 6-34 (2 folders))
- Tennessee Committee for the Humanities—Freedom of Choice, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-35)
- TAC Review, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-36)
- Interest Letters, 1981-1982. (Box-folder 6-37)
- Sponsor Negotiation Records (Unsuccessful/Contributors), 1981-1984. (Box-folder 6-38)
- Sponsor Negotiation Records (Contributors), 1981-1984. (Box-folder 6-39 to 6-40 (2 folders))
- Sponsor Negotiation Records, 1981-1984. (Box-folder 6-41 to 6-42 (2 folders))
- Hospitalization Insurance Forms, 1981-1984. (Box-folder 6-43)
- Organization's Contributions, 1981-1984. (Box-folder 6-44)
- Commerce Union Bank Loan, 1981-1986. (Box-folder 7-1)
- Sponsor Negotiations Records (Interest Sheets), 1982. (Box-folder 7-2)
- "Vanities," statement and letter, 1982. (Box-folder 7-3)
- Sponsor Negotiation Records (Unsuccessful), 1982. (Box-folder 7-4)
- Press Releases, 1982. (Box-folder 7-5)
- Contracts and Technical Information, 1982. (Box-folder 7-6)
- FEDAPT/TCG, 1982. (Box-folder 7-7)
- Letters, 1982. (Box-folder 7-8)
- March Touring, 1982. (Box-folder 7-9)
- One Potato, Two, 1982. (Box-folder 7-10)
- September and October Touring, 1982. (Box-folder 7-11)
- ROCO Promotions, 1982. (Box-folder 7-12)
- Opportunity Resources in the Arts, 1982. (Box-folder 7-13)
- T&M Communications, 1982. (Box-folder 7-14)
- TCH Income and Expenses, 1982. (Box-folder 7-15)
- One Potato, Two—Technical evaluation, 1982. (Box-folder 7-16)
- One Potato, Two—Program notes, 1982. (Box-folder 7-17)
- April Touring, 1982. (Box-folder 7-18)
- Freedom of Choice, 1982. (Box-folder 7-19)
- Fall Tour Evaluations, 1982. (Box-folder 7-20)
- Bank Card Statements, 1982. (Box-folder 7-21)
- One Potato, Two, 1982. (Box-folder 7-22)
- National Endowment for the Arts Expansion Arts Program FY1982, 1982. (Box-folder 7-23)
- Georgia Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-24)
- Miscellaneous Receipts, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-25)
- Florida Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-26)
- Indiana, Illinois, and Wisconsin Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-27)
- Mississippi Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-28)
- Massachusetts, Connecticut, and Rhode Island Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-29)
- Maine, Vermont, and New Hampshire Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-30)
- New York and New Jersey Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-31)
- Pennsylvania Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-32)
- South Carolina Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-33)
- West Virginia Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-34)
- Virginia Interest Records, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-35)
- Miscellaneous Areas, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-36)
- Sales Reports (Rough), 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-37)
- Kentucky Performances, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-38)
- North Carolina Performances, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-39 to 7-40 (2 folders))
- Ohio and Michigan Performances, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-41)
- Monthly Financial Reports, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-42)
- Tennessee Performances, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-43)
- Art Auction, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-44)
- Delivery Receipts, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-45)
- SAF Proposal, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-46)
- Interest letters, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-47)
- Media Expenses, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-48)
- Tax Documents, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-49)
- Programs, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-50)
- National Endowment for the Arts, Grant Application, 1982-1983. (Box-folder 7-51)
- Contracts and Technical Information, 1982-1984. (Box-folder 7-52 to 7-54 (3 folders))
- Touring Press Releases, 1983. (Box-folder 7-55)
- Fall Tour, 1983. (Box-folder 7-56 to 7-57 (2 folders))
- Winter tour, 1983. (Box-folder 8-1)
- Fall tour evaluations, 1983. (Box-folder 8-2)
- Royalties for "Vanities," 1983. (Box-folder 8-3)
- Spring tour, 1983. (Box-folder 8-4)
- Fall tour, 1983. (Box-folder 8-5)
- TCG Symposium, 1983. (Box-folder 8-6)
- Canceled Contracts, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-7)
- Virginia Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-8)
- Miscellaneous Interest Records, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-9)
- Miscellaneous, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-10)
- Pictures from One Potato, Two, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-11)
- Pictures from Golddust, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-12)
- Pictures from Happy Ever After, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-13)
- Financial Statements, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-14)
- Income Tax Papers, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-15)
- Board Meeting, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-16)
- SAF Proposal, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-17)
- Financial Audits, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-18)
- West Virginia Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-19)
- South Carolina Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-20)
- Louisiana Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-21)
- Mississippi Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-22)
- Pennsylvania Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-23)
- Georgia Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-24)
- North Carolina Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-25)
- New York and New Jersey Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-26)
- New England Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-27)
- Indiana, Illinois, and Wisconsin Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-28)
- Delaware, Maryland, and Washington DC Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-29)
- Florida Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-30)
- Alabama Performances, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-31)
- Letters, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-32)
- General Tour Information, 1983-1984. (Box-folder 8-33)
- Cover Letters, 1983-1985. (Box-folder 8-34)
- Credit Card Authorizations, 1983-1986. (Box-folder 8-35)
- Bidder Listings, 1983-1987. (Box-folder 8-36)
- Veterans' Administration Medical Center Theater, 1983-1988. (Box-folder 8-37)
- Bank Reconciliations, 1983-1988. (Box-folder 8-38 to 8-39 (2 folders))
- Past Fundraising Campaign letters, 1983-1988. (Box-folder 8-40)
- General Ledger, 1983-1988. (Box-folder 8-41)
- Miscellaneous information about Roots, 1983-1989. (Box-folder 8-42)
- Acknowledgment Letters, 1983-1991. (Box-folder 8-43)
- Sponsor Information, 1984. (Box-folder 8-44)
- Solicited Scripts, 1984. (Box-folder 8-45)
- Letters, 1984. (Box-folder 8-46)
- Canterbury Tales Script, 1984. (Box-folder 8-47)
- Comforts of Home, 1984. (Box-folder 8-48)
- Roots Grant, 1984. (Box-folder 8-49)
- Rummage Sale Records, 1984. (Box-folder 8-50)
- Art Auction, 1984. (Box-folder 8-51)
- Board/Staff organization meetings, 1984. (Box-folder 8-52)
- Spring Tour Evaluations, 1984. (Box-folder 8-53)
- Tenseness Revenue Sales Tax, 1984. (Box-folder 8-54)
- Showtime Search, 1984. (Box-folder 8-55)
- Cultural Arts Curriculum Committee, 1984. (Box-folder 8-56)
- The Roots Budget, 1984. (Box-folder 8-57)
- Alternate Roots Financial Statements, 1984. (Box-folder 8-58)
- Royalties for Golddust, 1984. (Box-folder 8-59)
- Tour Information, 1984. (Box-folder 8-60)
- OSHA, 1984. (Box-folder 9-1)
- Pistols, 1984. (Box-folder 9-2)
- Hamilton Bank Loans, 1984. (Box-folder 9-3)
- Donors, 1984. (Box-folder 9-4)
- OTR Information and Contracts (Fall Tour), 1984. (Box-folder 9-5)
- OTR Information and Contracts (Spring Tour), 1984. (Box-folder 9-6 to 9-9 (4 folders))
- Income Tax Papers, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-10)
- Financial Audit, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-11)
- Miscellaneous, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-12)
- Pictures from "My Sister in This House," 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-13)
- Pictures of "Adjoining Trances," 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-14)
- Sponsor Negotiation Records, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-15)
- Letters of Response, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-16)
- Georgia Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-17)
- West Virginia Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-18)
- Roots in Europe, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-19)
- Financial Statements, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-20)
- South Carolina Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-21)
- Pennsylvania Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-22)
- Ohio and Michigan Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-23)
- New York and New Jersey Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-24)
- New England Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-25)
- Kentucky Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-26)
- Indiana and Illinois Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-27)
- Florida Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-28)
- Delaware, Maryland, and Washington D.C. Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-29)
- North Carolina Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-30)
- Alabama Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-31)
- Mississippi Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-32)
- Virginia Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-33)
- Tennessee Performances, 1984-1985. (Box-folder 9-34)
- Outlines and fact sheets, 1984-1986. (Box-folder 9-35)
- New Alchemy Institute, 1984-1986. (Box-folder 9-36)
- NEA Theater, 1984-1986. (Box-folder 9-37)
- Royalty Agreements for "Blind Desire," 1984, 1988. (Box-folder 9-38)
- Theater Communications Group, Inc. (TCG) Surveys, 1984-1992. (Box-folder 9-39)
- Letters, 1984-1994. (Box-folder 9-40)
- Carpetbag Theater, Inc., 1985. (Box-folder 9-41)
- Script Request for "Jacques Brel," 1985. (Box-folder 9-42)
- Royalties for "My Sister in This House," 1985. (Box-folder 9-43)
- State Law of Tennessee, 1985. (Box-folder 9-44)
- Comprehensive Employment and Training Act (CETA) Audit, 1985. (Box-folder 9-45)
- Business Campaign, 1985. (Box-folder 9-46)
- Contributors, 1985. (Box-folder 9-47)
- IRS 8300 Forms, 1985. (Box-folder 9-48)
- Early Bird Sales, 1985. (Box-folder 9-49)
- Tax Records, 1985. (Box-folder 9-50)
- Volunteers, 1985. (Box-folder 9-51)
- Letters, 1985. (Box-folder 9-52)
- Fall Tour Evaluations, 1985. (Box-folder 9-53)
- OTR Information and Contracts (Spring Tour), 1985. (Box-folder 9-54)
- OTR Information and Contracts (Fall Tour), 1985. (Box-folder 9-55)
- SAF Touring Sales and Booking Information, 1985. (Box-folder 9-56)
- Letters, 1985. (Box-folder 9-57)
- Tennessee Arts Commission: Touring Program, 1985-1986. (Box-folder 9-58)